{
    "id": "5e90c1732efb40c78999a73999b3222d",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We usually go to Singapore on a holiday, but this year we ................................... to Bangkok.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed2363380693495dacb847937d8cf41e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Heat expands and cold ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "contract",
                "contracts",
                "will contract"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48e1553be25b42d1841d2638fc2d2956"
        },
        {
            "question": "A good player ....................................... every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "practice",
                "practices",
                "practiced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14eac4a39315405ebc8b2350e167ba24"
        },
        {
            "question": "John usually ....................................... coffee in the morning, but today he ................................ tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drinks, drinks",
                "drinks, drank",
                "drank, drinks"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "751b3be4a4dd4c8b965e48232d0841dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ................................ from pneumonia since last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "suffers",
                "has been suffering",
                "suffered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b67b9600d82b4beabc15e558603a1b17"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ............................................ a novel since October last, and he is about to finish it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "has been writing",
                "is writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc8e2c1396ec4c99ab6741a88b48a144"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he ........................................... hard, he will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "will work",
                "worked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b1abeb8ded043969bfae41521272113"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................................... you if I had had money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will help",
                "would help",
                "would have helped"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab9e8a6fd5624f2d85d10b9f56a0f55a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Time and tide ........................................... for no man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "waits",
                "will wait"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "148df152709a471e96ba98bf8073a97f"
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time next year he .......................................... the construction of his house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will complete",
                "will have completed",
                "would complete"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aeb57da5b4641ffa196e26b2571d211"
        }
    ]
}